Guide to the Terry L. Karl papers SC1353
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Terry L. Karl papers
1971-2008
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Karl, Terry Lynn, 1947-
SC1353
4.5 Linear Feet 3 cartons
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Terry L. Karl, 2017.
Biographical / Historical
Terry L. Karl is a professor of Political Science at Stanford University. She also serves as the Gildred Professor of Latin American Studies; William and Gretchen Kimball University Fellow; and Senior Research Scholar (by courtesty) with the Freeman Spogli Institute for International Studies/Center on Democracy, Development, and the Rule of Law.
Scope and Contents
Collection includes Karl's teaching materials from Political Science and Latin American Studies, as well as papers written by Karl.
Karl, Terry Lynn, 1947-; Karl, Terry Lynn, 1947-; Karl, Terry Lynn, 1947-
- Papers
  - Democratization Around the Globe, 1992 Nov (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - What Democracy Is…, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Comparing Neo-Democracies (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Bottom of the Barrel, 2003-jun (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Modes of Transition in South and Central America, Southern Europe and Eastern Europe, 1990-nov (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Conceptual Travels of Transitologists and Consolidologists (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Death and Rebirth in El Salvador, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Democracy in the World (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Fueling the 21st Century: The New Political Economy of Energy, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Course Readings for Political Science, 1991-1993 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Misc. Political Science Courses, 1988-2007 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Exercises and Examinations, 1971-1982 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Political Science 114K The Political Economy of Development (1 of 3), 1988 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Political Science 126K The United States in Central America (1 of 2), 1988 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Political Science 126K The United States in Central America (2 of 2), 1987 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Political Science 114K The Political Economy of Development (2 of 3), 1987 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Political Science 114K The Political Economy of Development (3 of 3), 1988 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Political Science 221K Course Reader Vol 1, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Political Science 221K Course Reader Vol 2, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Political Science 341T Seminar on Comparative Democratization Vol. II, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Political Science 316B Comparative Democratization Vol. 1, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Political Science 316B Comparative Democratization Vol. 2, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Political Science 227K Democratization: East, West, and South Vol.1, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Political Science 227K Democratization: East, West, and South Vol.2, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Taller Sobre Democratizacion Santiago de Chile Course Reader Vol.1, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Taller Sobre Democratizacion Santiago de Chile Course Reader Vol.2, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Luis Fraga Tribute Night, 2007 May 04 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Political Science 141 The Global Politics of Human Rights, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Political Science 43N Oil, Regime Change and Conflict Vol. 1, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Center for Latin American Studies Enlace, 1995-1999 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Information on Latin American Studies at Stanford, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Econ. And History Course Readings, 1974-1989 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Political Science Course Readings, 1985-1993 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Latin American Studies 250, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Course Proposal / Draft Syllabus: Women, Gender and Social Movements in Latin America (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Prof. Fraga A book of reflections, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Political Science 43N Oil, Regime Change and Conflict Vol. 2, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Political Science 141 The Global Politics of Human Rights Vol. 1, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Political Science 141 The Global Politics of Human Rights Vol. 2, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Political Science 141 The Global Politics of Human Rights, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 14)